{
    "subject": "resource/Nightfall_Games",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/Jared_Earle",
    "human_readable": "Jared Earle is a key person associated with Nightfall Games.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8978976607322693,
            "question": "What role does Jared Earle play at Nightfall Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566295504570007,
            "question": "Who is Jared Earle associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6685817241668701,
            "question": "What company is Jared Earle a key person for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6358588337898254,
            "question": "Is Jared Earle involved in game development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251311898231506,
            "question": "Are there any other notable people associated with Nightfall Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4807162880897522,
            "question": "What is Nightfall Games known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3366166949272156,
            "question": "Where is Nightfall Games based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33502480387687683,
            "question": "Can you name any games developed by Nightfall Games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3167371153831482,
            "question": "What genre of games does Nightfall Games develop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20614299178123474,
            "question": "Has Nightfall Games won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jared Earle is a key person associated with Nightfall Games.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6608_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of games does Nightfall Games develop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6608_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any games developed by Nightfall Games?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6608_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Nightfall Games based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6608_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6608_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Jared Earle was one of the founding members of Nightfall Games, and that he co-founded Nightfall Games with Dave Allsop and Mark Rapson. This information supports the triple that Jared Earle is a key person associated with Nightfall Games."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Jared Earle was one of the founding members of Nightfall Games and has contributed to the company's projects, indicating he is indeed a key person associated with Nightfall Games."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}